Anyway, Tani's watching the perimeter.
谷哥會幫忙注意周圍
We can concentrate on the front lines.
我們能集中精神在前面
We might wrack up a lot of kills.
或許可以趁機多殺一點
My head is killing me…
頭好痛…
Especially on the next map.
特別是下張地圖…
And why do I keep hearing someone's voice?
從剛才就聽到有人在說話…
I told you, I'm not turning the camera on.
我就說不開鏡頭了
Who's there?
是誰？
Quit pestering me.
你很煩耶
Sorry, I have to step away.
抱歉，我離開一下
I'll be right back.
馬上回來
What's…
這是…
going on?
怎麼回事？
-Excuse me… -Yes?!
-那個… -什麼事？
Um…
我想想…
DATA POINT 1: DRUNKEN MEMORY LOSS
（情報1：醉到沒有記憶）
Did I…?
我…
DATA POINT 2: UNFAMILIAR BEDROOM
（情報2：陌生的房間）
Don't tell me this is…
難不成我…
DATA POINT 3: SKIN EXPOSED
（情報3：暴露的肌膚）
DATA POINT 4: MALE, YAMADA
（情報4：男人，山田）
Is this a one-night stand?!
因為一時意亂情迷犯了錯？
-Does it look that way? -Unfortunately!
-你覺得看起來像嗎？ -不太像！
ORIGINAL STORY BY MASHIRO
（原作：Mashiro）
To summarize…
簡單來說就是…
It was either carry you home…
看是要選擇照顧你
IZAKAYA BOTTA
（博大居酒屋）
…or dump you in the street.
還是直接把你丟在路邊
Even I thought that would be unethical.
但我想後者實在太不人道
I'm truly sorry.
實在非常抱歉
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT, THOUGH
（但我還是煩惱了很久）
I promise to repay--
這份恩情我一定會報…
If you leave immediately, that'll do.
你現在立刻回去就夠了
Right! I'll leave immediately!
遵命，我現在立刻回去
By the way, your clothes were covered in vomit.
話說你吐滿穢物的衣服
You'll find them washed in the bathroom.
我洗好掛在浴室裡曬
Oh, and… I paid your bill at the izakaya.
還有…我幫忙付了居酒屋的帳
I'll pay you back immediately!
我馬上付清給你！
This is bad…
糟糕…
Excuse me, um…
請問…
Where is the bathroom?
浴室怎麼走？
Out the door, to your right.
出去右轉
I'm never going to live this down.
這個人情欠得真大…
Well,
就這樣
I doubt we'll meet again, but…
我想以後應該不會再見面了
Take care.
請你保重
What a mess.
真是醜態百出
On top of it all, I spent the night in the room of a guy I just met.
而且還在初次見面的男生家過夜
Mom, if you hear me in Gunma, I'm sorry.
在群馬的媽媽，對不起了
I'm beat.
累死我了
I'd better do some schoolwork.
還得要寫作業才行
Hey…
奇怪？
Wasn't I…
我…
wearing a necklace?
應該有戴項鍊吧？
Um, why is it gone?
怪了？為什麼不在了？
It's not here.
不見了
Your clothes were covered in vomit.
你吐滿穢物的衣服
You'll find them washed in the bathroom.
我洗好掛在浴室裡曬
Don't tell me…
難不成…
I dropped it in Yamada's apartment?
掉在山田的房間了？
SYSTEM: AKANE HAS LOGGED IN
（Akane上線了）
Oh! Hi there, Akane!
Akane，哈囉
GUILD: CHOCOLATE RABBIT GUILDMASTER: PRINCESS RURI
（公會“巧克力兔” 公會會長：瑠璃姬）
Hi there, Princess Ruri!
瑠璃姬，哈囉
Yamada… What about Yamada?
山田？山田人呢？
OFFLINE MEMBERS: I LOVE BEEF, YAMADA, MATCHA PUDDING, TAKEZO
（離線會員）
He's offline.
沒上線…
I know I had it on at the izakaya.
我記得在居酒屋時還戴著
If I lost it, it must have been after that.
要掉的話，就是在那之後
It really must have been when I took my clothes off in Yamada's room.
果然只能是在山田家脫衣服時掉的
What do I do?
怎麼辦？
That necklace
那條項鍊…
was the first gift I ever got from Takuma.
是拓馬送我的第一份禮物
What's this?
奇怪？
Akane, are you frozen?
Akane當機了？
You don't seem to be in good spirits.
今天是不是沒精神？
AKANE: I HAVE A LOT GOING ON IRL.
（我在現實中發生了不少事）
RURI: OH? TROUBLE OF SOME KIND?
（哎呀呀…遇到麻煩了？）
AKANE: SOMETHING LIKE THAT…
（差不多…）
Ruri will listen, if you like!
瑠璃願意聽你說哦
I'm the Guild Master, after all.
瑠璃是大家的會長
You can depend on me!
儘管依靠我吧
You're so cute, Princess Ruri.
瑠璃姬永遠都好可愛
SO SOOTHING…
（獲得療癒了…）
I see.
原來如此啊
Your boyfriend broke up with you
被男友甩了
and you lost a memento.
還弄丟了珍惜的飾品啊
I understand.
我懂你的心情啊
My fans give me all sorts of presents,
人家也常收到很多粉絲送的禮物
and they're all precious to me.
每一份都很重要啊
They have memories attached, right?
都有留下不同回憶嘛
SHE HAS… LOTS OF FANS…
（粉絲…很多禮物…）
Although I'm running out of space to store them in.
只是最近快要沒地方放了
Wow…
好驚人
IT'S A CRIME TO BE CUTE
（長得可愛真是罪孽）
SYSTEM: YAMADA HAS LOGGED IN
（山田上線了）
Hi there, Yamada-kun!
山田，哈囉
Hi.
你好
Yamada's here!
山田來了！
Now then…
那個…
-Say, Yamada-kun… -Yamada! Hey, Yamada!
-山田 -山田…
-Join us for some love gossip. -Ya… Yamada…
-你也來聊聊戀愛話題吧 -山…山田
I can't. The bosses should be appearing soon.
沒辦法，現在是BOSS出沒的時間
You're hunting bosses again?
又要去打BOSS？
It's double-reward season.
現在有雙倍獎勵
Really?! For how long?
到什麼時候？
YAMADA: THIS WEEK ONLY
（到這星期）
RURI: I DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE!
（是哦？我都沒發現）
She's so excited, I can't even get a word in.
他們聊得太熱烈，完全沒辦法插話
I'll try a private chat.
只好去個人聊天室了
AKANE: YAMADA!!!!!! I MAY HAVE LOST MY NECKLACE AT YOUR PLACE. SEEN IT?!
（山田！我的項鍊好像掉在你家 你有看到嗎？）
Oh, did he notice?
他注意到訊息了？
YAMADA: NO.
（沒看到）
That was quick.
回得有夠快
Did he even…?
可以多確認一下吧
Yamada-kun, come chat with us.
山田也一起來聊天
It will cheer Akane up.
來安慰Akane吧
-Rather not. -You're awful!
-才不要 -好過分
More importantly,
比起那種事
the guild treasure chest…
這個公會的倉庫…
It's always so full, I can't use it.
每次都塞滿道具，我沒辦法用
Huh?
哎呀
Oh, you're right! There are a lot of items inside!
真的耶，滿滿都是道具
I haven't been checking it.
我最近完全沒查看
I'm always cleaning it out,
我每次都會整理
but it fills up before I know it.
一不注意就滿成這樣
That's strange. I wonder why?
什麼啊，好神秘
If it's not in Yamada's apartment,
如果不在山田家
could it be at the izakaya?
果然是掉在居酒屋嗎？
Maybe someone thinks they're being helpful by putting items in.
是誰好心放道具進去的嗎？
-Oh, that was me-- -What?!
-那是我… -什麼？
This garbage is "helpful"?
放這些垃圾叫好心？
You don't have to call it garbage.
說是垃圾太過分了
A guild member must be putting items in the chest to help beginners.
一定是有公會成員為了新手特別放的
Even someone who started three minutes ago
就算是三分鐘剛加入的新手
would have better equipment than this.
身上的裝備絕對都比這些好
Now, now…
別這樣說啦
What if the guild members were online?
如果那個成員在線上怎麼辦？
They'd be shocked if they read this chat.
他看到聊天室一定會大受打擊
It was me.
是我
AKANE: IT WAS ME. I THOUGHT BEGINNERS COULD USE EQUIPMENT I NO LONGER NEEDED.
（想說把不用的防具和裝備 留給新手成員…）
AKANE: SORRY, I GUESS IT'S IN THE WAY.
（抱歉…我礙到大家了吧…）
RURI: THAT'S NOT TRUE! YOU'RE SO KIND, AKANE!
（沒那回事！ Akane果然心地善良！）
-It's in the way. -Yamada-kun!
-礙事 -山田！
I'm the one who's been forced to clean up that garbage.
每次都是我在整理那些垃圾
Stop calling it "garbage"!
不要說是垃圾！
Akane only did it to be helpful!
Akane只是出自一片好心
Please be more selective.
請你懂得做取捨
Storage space is limited.
空間不是無限的
Yamada-kun!
山田！
Don't be mean! You have to choose your words better!
真是受不了你，拜託你口氣好一點
Naughty!
你這樣不行啦，不行！
SYSTEM: AKANE HAS LOGGED OUT.
（Akane下線了）
RURI: OH NO…
（山田是大笨蛋）
RURI: BE NICER TO AKANE!
（Akane還不習慣玩遊戲）
RURI: SHE'S NOT A GAMER, YOU KNOW!
（對她溫柔一點啦！）
That hurt.
好痛…
CRUNCH?
（什麼？）
Did I step on something?
好像踩到什麼了
Seriously?
不會吧？
I hate you, Yamada!
討厭死山田了
Akane…
茜…
I'm sorry.
抱歉
I was out of line.
都是我的錯
I finally see it now.
我終於清醒了
Takuma…
拓馬…
This is for you.
這個…
An apology present.
是我聊表歉意的禮物
I hope you'll accept it.
希望你收下
I'm really happy, Takuma!
拓馬，我好高興
Takuma…
拓馬…
Takuma!
拓馬！
A nightmare…
作惡夢了
Sounds more like a prophetic dream.
與其說是惡夢，根本是現實
Momo, are you enjoying this?
小桃，你是不是覺得很好玩？
Not really.
才沒那回事
I'm actually sick of hearing about Takuma.
我也開始聽膩拓馬的話題了
That was a fake laugh too.
我剛才只是配合笑笑
On the other hand,
別說那個了
I'd love to hear more about the hot online game otaku.
我比較想聽電玩迷帥哥的話題
You really spent the night with him
你們共度了一晚
and nothing happened?
真的什麼都沒發生？
That again?
又是這件事？
I told you, nothing happened.
我就說沒有了
He was just doing a good deed.
對山田來說只是舉手之勞
That reminds me,
說到這，就讓我想起來
what do I do about Takuma's necklace?
拓馬的項鍊該怎麼辦？
I'm sure I lost it at Yamada's apartment.
我覺得應該是掉在山田家
What good is a present from the guy who cast you aside?
他都甩了你，留戀禮物做什麼？
CAST ASIDE
（甩了自己）
Just get over it.
你也太放不下了
GET OVER IT
（放不下）
You've always been like that, Akane.
你的個性就是這樣
You prioritize your boyfriends over your social life,
所有行程優先配合男友
and you even start playing dumb online games for them.
為了男友玩起沒興趣的線上遊戲
Now that you mention it, didn't you start
話說剛交往時
making lunch for him after your first date?
你是不是還親手為他做便當？
It's all too heavy.
你的愛實在太沉重了
I'll stop talking about Takuma.
我不會再聊拓馬了
Please forgive me.
拜託你饒了我
Live and learn.
你懂就好
It's already six, huh?
六點了啊
Time to head home, do my laundry, and…
回去先洗衣服，然後…
I wonder what's on TV tonight.
今天有什麼電視節目啊？
My nights are free now.
晚上真閒
Playing that game alone is boring too.
一個人玩遊戲也很無聊
It's in the way.
礙事
I haven't logged in since that day.
我從那之後就沒再上線了
I wonder if that surly afro-head
那個討人厭的爆炸頭
is still his addict self.
不曉得有沒有繼續沉迷遊戲？
I'm sorry, Akito…
抱歉哦，秋斗
I called you here,
抱歉，明明是我叫住你
so I should get to the point.
我卻扭扭捏捏
I, um… well…
那個…就是…
You see…
聽我說…
High-school kids…
高中生…
She must be asking him out.
是在準備告白吧
Those were the days.
這麼青春真好
I'll bet the guy is popular.
這位小哥真受歡迎
I confessed to my high school senpai like that too.
我高中時也有像那樣跟學長告白
-I like you! -I have a girlfriend.
-我喜歡你 -我有女友了
That hottie, Saito…
帥氣的齋藤學長
I wonder how he's doing.
不曉得過得如何？
BITTERSWEET MEMORIES…
（淡淡的回憶）
So, um…
那個…
How much longer?
還沒好嗎？
It's been about seven minutes since you stopped me.
你叫住我之後，已經過七分鐘了
Can you do some bullet points
你可以先整理好重點
and contact me another day?
過幾天再跟我說嗎？
If you don't mind, the bosses should be appearing soon.
抱歉，快到BOSS出沒的時間了
Excuse me, then.
我先走了
Hold it right there!
等一下！
COULDN'T HELP IT…
（脫口而出）
That figures. You've already forgotten.
也是啦，你肯定忘了吧
It's me, Akane. The one you helped at the online game event.
我是參加遊戲活動時受你照顧的茜
Oh, the lady who got wasted and threw up in my room.
是那個在我家醉到吐的大姐
I really am sorry about that!
上次真的很抱歉
No, wait…
不是啦
Wasn't he a bit rude?
山田也太過分了吧？
She was obviously trying to ask you out.
人家怎麼看都是要告白吧
Couldn't you let her finish?
你聽她說到最後嘛
I…
我…
was being asked out?
剛才被告白了嗎？
You know…
我說你
you'd be better off learning about people's emotions than video games.
比起遊戲，更應該學著察言觀色吧？
I'm often told that.
常有人這麼說
-So you're a high school student, huh? -Yeah.
-原來山田是高中生啊 -是的
That's why you only ordered soft drinks at the izakaya.
這麼說起來 你在居酒屋都在喝果汁嘛
Yeah.
是的
What year are you?
你幾年級？
I'm a senior.
三年級
Hey, he's wearing the uniform for Tosei Academy.
話說他是穿東成學院的制服嘛
That means he's smart.
原來山田很聰明啊
That school is a nightmare to get into.
那間學校超難考的
Actually…
其實…
I was hoping to meet you again.
我很想再見大姐你一面
Sorry.
抱歉
I found it later,
我在那之後有找到
but I had stepped on it.
但是卻踩壞了
The heart…
心型…
split cleanly in two.
斷成了兩半…
Thank you for taking the time.
謝謝你特別拿給我
Have you been carrying it since then?
你一直隨身帶著嗎？
You mentioned we use the same train station.
聽說我們住同個車站附近
I thought I might run into you.
我就想應該有機會見到
I guess I should have logged in, huh?
早知道我就上線了
It must have been a pain.
你應該很困擾吧？
No.
不會
Well, thanks!
謝謝你
I was gonna throw it out, anyway, so don't worry.
我原本就打算丟了，你不用在意
I'm off then.
那我先走了
Excuse me…
那個…
Here… please take it.
這給你用
I don't need it back.
可以不用還我
Now, if you don't mind…
就這樣，失陪了
Here's the forecast for the Kanto area. Yesterday's rain moved north,
關東從昨天開始，雨勢逐漸往北
so today will be sunny.
今天是晴朗好天氣
Tonight will offer a clear view of the moon.
晚上能看到美麗滿月…
Here… please take it.
這給你用
I was gonna throw it out, anyway,
我原本就打算丟了
so don't worry.
你不用在意
Coming!
來了
TAGAWA EXPRESS MOVING COMPANY
（田川宅急便）
-Hello, you have a delivery!
你好，我們是宅急便
The sender is "Ms. Kinoshita."
這些是木之下寄來的東西
We'll carry them inside!
我們幫忙搬進屋裡哦
Thanks for your business!
謝謝關照
"Dear Akane, I'm turning your bedroom
“茜在老家的房間
into an exercise room."
媽媽想改成自己的健身房
"Here are all your things."
就把你的東西都寄過去了
"Love, Mom."
請多指教…”
So…
然後呢？
Why'd you call me?
幹嘛叫我來？
I JUST GOT HOME FROM WORK
（我剛打完工耶）
You've gotta help me, Momo!
小桃，救救我
I can't even walk in here.
家裡亂到不能走路了
My mom sent my things from home.
老家突然寄了我的東西來
Just look at all this stuff!
這些量也太誇張了吧？
What do I do?!
我該怎麼辦啊？
I'm exhausted. Everything goes.
煩死了，全部丟掉
Starting with that huge teddy--
首先從那隻大熊開始
Wait! That's a memento.
等等，那充滿了回憶
-It's from my grandmother-- -Shut up!
-有我和奶奶的回憶… -給我閉嘴！
-My Grandma's-- -There, next!
-奶奶… -好，下一個！
Next!
下一個！
Akane!
茜
These two things are in the way.
這個和這個太礙事了
What do I do with them?
該收到哪裡啊？
The umbrella's new, so it can be used,
傘還很新，你會繼續用吧？
but the necklace is broken.
項鍊…
Can I throw it out?
反正都壞了，可以丟掉嗎？
Please be more selective.
請你懂得做取捨
Storage space is limited.
空間不是無限的
-"Be selective"… -Huh?
-要懂得取捨… -什麼？
CAREFUL, I'LL THROW THEM BOTH OUT
（小心我全丟哦）
No matter how precious,
每個重要的東西
I can't hang on to everything.
無法全都留下來
COMBUSTIBLES - NON-COMBUSTIBLES
（可燃垃圾，不可燃垃圾）
So, in the end…
結果…
you're keeping that one?
那個還是沒丟啊
Even so…
但是…
I'm discarding everything else.
其他全都丟了
After all…
因為…
I don't need it anymore.
都是不再需要的東西
THERE, THERE.
（好乖）
Okay!
好！
Let's cut loose and get some yakiniku!
去燒肉店大吃一頓吧！
Your treat, of course.
當然是茜請客
Cash flow is tight.
我現在財政緊迫
Please go easy on me.
還請你高抬貴手了
-Yes? -Yamada!
-來了 -山田
I came to return your umbrella!
我來還你傘囉
Oh, man.
討厭
He really is hot!
真的是個帥哥耶
The name's Momo.
我是小桃
So nice to meet you, Yamada-kun!
山田，幸會啊
GRR…
（不爽…）
Here you are!
來
Huh? Something wrong?
奇怪？你有煩惱嗎？
Um…
不…
I can't find the words.
我突然無話可說
Yamada-kun!
山田
I'm sorry Akane's always causing you trouble.
茜老是給你添麻煩，真抱歉哦
However…
不過…
If you'll have me, let's take this opportunity
如果你不嫌棄，希望能藉機…
and marry with the intention of dating!
以交往為前提和我結婚吧
I won't hesitate to call the police.
我是認真想報警了
SHE REEKS OF ALCOHOL…
（酒臭味…）
I told you I didn't need it back.
我說過不用還我了吧？
In fact, it's a nuisance.
這樣反而讓我很困擾
Well, you see…
那個…
It's not just the umbrella.
其實不只是傘
I also…
我…
wanted to thank you!
是來向你道謝的
On the day of that event,
遊戲活動那天
I'm really glad you were there.
幸好還有山田在
Had I been alone…
如果只有我
I would have really had it rough.
其實還蠻難受的
So, truly…
真的…
Are you okay?
你沒事吧？
Thank you!
謝謝你了
Oh.
喔
Bye, then!
就這樣
We'll head home before you call the police!
趁你還沒報警，我們先走了
Please do.
拜託了
Momo, time to go home!
小桃，我們回家吧
Walk with me now!
要好好走路哦
I'll walk.
我會走…
Momo, better watch your step!
小桃，小心樓梯哦
Watch step…
樓梯…
By the way…
話說…
Ruri…
瑠璃
The Guild Master was worried about you.
就是公會會長，他很擔心你
She said you hadn't logged in since then.
說你從那天之後就沒上線了
So…
所以…
If you… have the chance…
如果你有空的話…
I will!
我會上線的
I'll login.
立刻上線
Right when I get home!
我回去馬上登入
Will you too, Yamada?
山田也會來嗎？
No, I'm going to bed.
不，我要睡了
You won't?
你不上線嗎？
-Sleep. -You really won't?
-我要睡了 -不上線嗎？
I will… marry you.
要結婚
They multiplied…
增加了
What should we do, Yamada?
山田，怎麼辦？
Yamada?
山田？
Yoo-hoo!
喂
Hey, what's wrong?
喂，怎麼了？
Yamada?
山田